<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Job it</string>
    <string name="welcome_msg1">Dear  Sugar,</string>
    <string name="welcome_msg2"><font color='green'>Your Resume is ready and you found the best job announcement?</font>\n\n<b>Great</b>, select an amazing cover letter and let\'s Job It...</string>


    <string-array name="email_templates">"
    <item>Dear [recruiter],\n
Hoping my mail finds you well.\n
Kindly find my attached CV, appling for "[job]" available vacancy announced.\n
\n
Regards.\n
[name], [job]\n
[phone]"</item>
        <item>Dear [recruiter],\n
Good Day.\n
\n
I hope all is well on your side. Kindly accept my attached CV for the position "[job]", hoping it would meet your requirements.\n
I’m looking forward to further discuss this opportunity in person.\n
\n
Best Regards,\n
[name], [job]\n
[phone]</item>
        <item>Dear [recruiter],\n
\n
After best regards,my name is [name]\n
A graduate of [education]\n
I am sending to apply for the position [job]. Kindly find my CV attached.\n
\n
Best Regards.\n
Yours,\n
[name], [job]\n
[phone]</item>
        <item>Dear [recruiter],\n
Good day\n
 \n
In reference to the above mentioned subject, I am writing to know if there is an employment vacancy for an position in your organization relevant to my qualification and knowledge.\n​
I have attached a copy of my CV and I am available to attend an interview if given an opportunity.\n
\n
Thank you for your time and consideration.\n
\n
regards,\n
[name], [job]\n
[phone]</item>
        <item>Dear [recruiter],\n
\n
I hope this mail finds you well,\n
I would like to apply for the role of [job], that I have seen posted and promoted on your website.\n
I believe that this job aligns well with my qualities and strengths and that it would be a great opportunity for me to grow both personally and professionally.\n
\n
I look forward to hearing from you in the near future and hopefully to schedule an interview. Thank you for your time and consideration.\n
\n
please kindly see the attached CV.\n
\n
regards,\n
[name], [job]\n
[phone]</item>
        <item>Dear [recruiter]\n
I hope everything going well.\n
I am writing to express my interest in working in your company in the position of [job] where I can apply and enhance my academic background, skills, and career through working in creative and productive development team that aims to meet the company’s and customers’ requirements and satisfaction.\n
Now I would like to bring my skills and experience to work for your company.\n
The attached CV can serve to provide you with greater details of my education, skills, and experience.\n
Thank you for your time and consideration.\n
\n
regards,\n
[name], [job]\n
[phone]</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>